{
    "subject": "resource/Al-Ittihad_(Israeli_newspaper)",
    "predicate": "ontology/headquarter",
    "object": "resource/Haifa",
    "human_readable": "The headquarters of Al-Ittihad (Israeli newspaper) are located in Haifa.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9573908448219299,
            "question": "Where are the headquarters of Al-Ittihad newspaper located?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9259523749351501,
            "question": "In what city is Al-Ittihad newspaper headquartered?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7362060546875,
            "question": "Who owns or operates Al-Ittihad newspaper?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.701776385307312,
            "question": "What country is Al-Ittihad newspaper based in?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6047695875167847,
            "question": "What is the circulation of Al-Ittihad newspaper?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6030360460281372,
            "question": "Is Al-Ittihad a local or national newspaper?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5881171822547913,
            "question": "When was Al-Ittihad newspaper founded?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5035631060600281,
            "question": "What type of publication is Al-Ittihad?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.2558741271495819,
            "question": "Does Al-Ittihad have an online presence?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.22250406444072723,
            "question": "Does Al-Ittihad focus on specific topics like politics or sports?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The headquarters of Al-Ittihad (Israeli newspaper) are located in Haifa.",
            "html": "dbpedia_3780_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Does Al-Ittihad have an online presence?",
            "html": "dbpedia_3780_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What type of publication is Al-Ittihad?",
            "html": "dbpedia_3780_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=When was Al-Ittihad newspaper founded?",
            "html": "dbpedia_3780_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3780_105.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3780_108.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3780_16.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3780_17.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3780_40.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3780_57.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3780_60.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3780_69.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3780_80.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3780_91.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```  \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Based on the provided context information, here is the response:\n\n`{'output': 'yes'}`\n\nThe documents mention that \"Al Ittihad\" has its \"Headquarters in Haifa\"."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents state that \"Al-Ittihad (Arabic: \u00d8\u00a7\u00d9\u0084\u00d8\u00a7\u00d8\u00aa\u00d8\u00ad\u00d8\u00a7\u00d8\u00af) Israeli Arabic-language daily newspaper headquarters in Haifa,\" which supports the given statement."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Less Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}